

La Cala de Mijas Malaga, Spain

Tel: +34.648.245.868

Mail: Angeline.remy@hotmail.fr

Portfolio: https://aremy-web.github.io/cv/

ABOUT

I have several years of experience in the development of digital solutions. Over time, I have developed a particular interest in B2B technical software development.

I currently work as a fully integrated member of the scrum team in the agile environment, collaborating closely with the front-end and back-end developers.

EXPERIENCE

UX | UI Designer

The Workshop - Inventors of Play, Malaga - Spain

November 2021 - Present

UX | UI design considering the end-to-end process.

Focus on optimal usability and aesthetics.

Ensure the product meets the needs of the business.

Collaborate with the whole team - Development team and product team.

UX | UI and web developer

Ebike Malaga - VEM, Malaga - Spain

January 2019 - October 2021

UX | UI design: From wireframing to designing end-to-end flows and prototypes.

Determination of languages and framework requirements.

Web development complying with the established framework and SEO technique.

Testing and adjusting the website before deployment.

Updating web versions.

Fixing bugs and errors after deployment.

Creating visual elements for digital communication.

Digital Communication Executive

Ebike Malaga, Malaga - Spain

December 2016 - December 2018

Web analytics & digital communication strategy development.

Digital graphics creation.

Web content writing.

Social media management.

Customer service (Online & front desk).

Assistant Hotel Manager

Zatori, Collingwood - New Zealand

2015 - 2015

Digital communication.

General tasks assistance.

Office researcher urban planning

Franck Boutté Consultants, Nantes - France

2013 - 2014

Computer-aided micro-climate analysis and diagnosis of sustainable development in urban areas to complete the elaboration of the urban planning prescriptions.

CAD Designer

Paul Poirier & Associates, Nantes - France

2011 - 2012

Elaboration of architectural plans with Allplan, 2D and 3D models in accordance with the architect's and clients' requirements. Using Allplan, SketchUp and Photoshop.

Hospitality coordinator

Friendship Ambassadors Foundation Inc, NYC- USA

2010 - 2011

Hospitality coordinator for the participants of the "7th Annual Youth Assembly" at the United Nations, New York.

Mission leader - Environmental protection

Earth, Sea & Sky NGO, Zakinthos- Greece

2009 - 2010

Hospitality coordinator for the participants of the "7th Annual Youth Assembly" at the United Nations, New York.

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATION

Scrum foundation professional certificate - 2021

CertiProf - Credential ID 56494690

CAD designer, architecture - 2012

Aactes & Formations, Nantes, France

Master's degree, tourism management and international hotel business - 2010

Université de Perpignan Via Domitia

Master 1, economy, environment and sustainable development - 2009

UVSQ Université de Versailles Saint-Quentin-en-Yvelines

Languages

French: Native | English: Fluent | Spanish: Fluent